

I graduated from the Computer Engineering program in 2023, and during my studies, I developed mobile applications using Flutter for two years, both in academic projects and for personal development. After graduation, I gained in-depth experience in frontend development by working with React, TypeScript, and Tailwind CSS to create modern web applications for one and a half years. As a software developer who aims to add value to projects with my technical skills and continuously improve myself, I am excited to participate in innovative projects and contribute even more.

Work Experience

• 4/2023 - 9/2024

<u>Ciloğlu Handels - GmbH</u>: React TS Developer

• 3/2023 - 4/2023

<u>Çiloğlu Handels - GmbH</u>: Intern Flutter Developer

• 1/2023 - 3/2023

<u>Mediatriple</u> : Intern Flutter Developer

Education

2019-2023	Kocaeli University	Computer Engineering (Bachelor) - Graduate
2019-2022	Sakarya University	First and Emergency Aid (Associate) - Graduate
2018-2019	Konya Technical University	Computer Engineering (Bachelor) - Lateral Transfer

Profiles

Github	<u>OrhanKahraman.github</u>
Linkedin	OrhanKahraman.linkedin

Programming Languages

React TS	895
Flutter (Dart)	60
Python	%55

Languages **Skills**

Turkish	Native	Writing, reading, speaking	%100
<u>English</u>	B2	Writing, reading	%70

Personal Information

Birth Date: 02/05/2000 Place of Birth: Balıkesir/Turkey